{
    "data": [
        {
            "Question":"What happens when delete is called for a NULL pointer?",
            "Type":"Memory Allocation and Deallocation",
            "Answer":"No effect",
            "Answer 1":"No effect",
            "Answer 2":"Compiler error",
            "Answer 3":"Run-time crash"
        },
        {
            "Question":"Is it okay to call delete on a pointer twice?",
            "Type":"Memory Allocation and Deallocation",
            "Answer":"No",
            "Answer 1":"No",
            "Answer 2":"Yes",
            "Answer 3":"It depends"

        },
        {
            "Question":"How do you create a dynamic array of size 10?",
            "Type":"Memory Allocation and Deallocation",
            "Answer":"int* arr = new int[10];",
            "Answer 1":"int* arr = new int[10];",
            "Answer 2":"int** arr= new int*[10];",
            "Answer 3":"int arr= new int*[10];"
        },
        {
            "Question":"How do decalre a generic pointer?",
            "Type":"Memory Allocation and Deallocation",
            "Answer":"void*",
            "Answer 1":"void*",
            "Answer 2":"gen*",
            "Answer 3":"word*"
        },
        {
            "Question":"A reference declaration creates:",
            "Type":"Memory Allocation and Deallocation",
            "Answer":"A new variable",
            "Answer 1":"A new variable",
            "Answer 2":"An alis to an existing variable",
            "Answer 3":"A pointer"
        },
        {
            "Question":"The expression p = new int[20]:",
            "Type":"Memory Allocation and Deallocation",
            "Answer":"Allocates 20 integers and assigns the base address to p",
            "Answer 1":"Allocates 20 integers and assigns the base address to p",
            "Answer 2":"Assigns an integer of size 20 bytes",
            "Answer 3":"Assiiigns an integer of value 20"
        },
        {
            "Question":"After the decalaration const N = 5, which of the following is illegal?",
            "Type":"Memory Allocation and Deallocation",
            "Answer":"cin > >N",
            "Answer 1":"cin >> N",
            "Answer 2":"cout << N",
            "Answer 3":"if (N==i+2)"
        },
        {
            "Question":"Which of the following about using const is false?",
            "Type":"Memory Allocation and Deallocation",
            "Answer":"You cannot assign a pointer to a const value",
            "Answer 1":"You cannot assign a pointer to a const value",
            "Answer 2":"You cannot modify a const variable",
            "Answer 3":"A const variable must be initialized when declared"
        },
        {
            "Question":"Dynamic memory is allocated from which type of memory?",
            "Type":"Memory Allocation and Deallocation",
            "Answer":"Heap",
            "Answer 1":"Heap",
            "Answer 2":"Stack",
            "Answer 3":"Static"
        },
        {
            "Question":"In C++, dynamic memory allocation is done using:",
            "Type":"Memory Allocation and Deallocation",
            "Answer":"new operator",
            "Answer 1":"malloc()",
            "Answer 2":"new operator",
            "Answer 3":"cmallloc()"
        },
        {
                "Question":"What is the time complexity of Merge Sort?",
                "Type":"Algorithms",
                "Answer":"O(n log n)",
                "Answer 1":"O(n^3)",
                "Answer 2":"O(n log n)",
                "Answer 3":"O(1)"
        },
        {
                "Question":"Which of the following is not a graph algorithm?",
                "Type":"Algorithms",
                "Answer":"Quick Sort",
                "Answer 1":"Dijkstra",
                "Answer 2":"Floyd Warshall",
                "Answer 3":"Quick Sort"
        },
        {
                "Question":"Which data structure can be used to check for valid parantheses",
                "Type":"Algorithms",
                "Answer":"Stack",
                "Answer 1":"Queue",
                "Answer 2":"Heap",
                "Answer 3":"Stack"
        },
        {
                "Question":"Merge sort algorithm uses:",
                "Type":"Algorithms",
                "Answer":"Divide and Conquer",
                "Answer 1":"DP",
                "Answer 2":"Divide and Conquer",
                "Answer 3":"Binary Search"
        },
        {
                "Question":"Which algorithm is not stable?",
                "Type":"Algorithms",
                "Answer":"Selection Sort",
                "Answer 1":"Selection Sort",
                "Answer 2":"Merge Sort",
                "Answer 3":"Bubble Sort"
        },
        {
                "Question":"Which of the following uses memoization?",
                "Type":"Algorithms",
                "Answer":"Dynamic Programming",
                "Answer 1":"Divide and Conquer",
                "Answer 2":"Dynamic Programming",
                "Answer 3":"Greedy approach"
        },
        {
                "Question":"Which algorithm does not divide the list?",
                "Type":"Algorithms",
                "Answer":"Linear search",
                "Answer 1":"Binary search",
                "Answer 2":"Linear search",
                "Answer 3":"Merge sort"
        },
        {
                "Question":"Which data structure is used to perform recursion?",
                "Type":"Algorithms",
                "Answer":"Stack",
                "Answer 1":"Queue",
                "Answer 2":"Heap",
                "Answer 3":"Stack"
        },
        {
                "Question":"Which approach is followed in Floyd Warshall Algorithm?",
                "Type":"Algorithms",
                "Answer":"Dynamic Programming",
                "Answer 1":"Dynamic Programming",
                "Answer 2":"Greedy approach",
                "Answer 3":"Randomization"
        },
        {
                "Question":"Hamiltonian Path problem is:",
                "Type":"Algorithms",
                "Answer":"NP Complete",
                "Answer 1":"P",
                "Answer 2":"NP Complete",
                "Answer 3":"Just NP"
        }

    ]
}
